

# **ALEX VERON**

**Full Stack Developer** 

☑ alexveron1108@gmail.com

Hougang, Singapore 530515

in www.linkedin.com/in/alex-veron-7a26a01b4/



daylight1019.github.io

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Experienced Full Stack Developer with 5 years in the industry and high-level proficiency in the following programs: C/C++, C#, Java, React Native, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, WordPress, Shopify, Laravel, CodeIgniter, AngularJS, NodeJS, ReactJS, Vue.JS, ASP.NET to establish a career as Full Stack Developer.

I am very familiar and experience with Mobile Application (native and hybrid) and Web Application Architecture and have worked with a good number of successful development teams.

I am always striving to explore new technologies and look to ways to improve my skills in this rapidly changing industry.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Belacam

Belacam Inc.

**Business Friend Inc.** 

Mar 2019 - Apr 2020

Belacam.com is a social media site. The centerpiece of the platform is a familiar content sharing system. Belacam is used just like Instagram - users post their own photos and videos, follow each other, and give likes. As a project lead developer, I managed backend and frontend developers and designers for making web site for this company.

Technologies used:

Angular Python/Django JavaScript HTML/jQuery PostgresSQL

#### **Business Friend**

Oct 2017 - Feb 2019

As a website developer, I developed Business Friend which is redefining how you connect with your professional and social network. By developing this large web site, I demonstrated my back-end web skills. This site is a social networking and communications utility that helps you say connection with the people and professionals that matter the most.

Technologies used:

Angular PHP/Codelgniter HTML/jQuery Bootstrap

# Free contractor estimate & invoice maker

Jun 2016 - Sep 2017

As a Team Leader, I managed and developed React Native app what is for easy estimate and invoice maker for sending invoices and estimates to your customers. It has wonderful features. With contractor simple, you'll be invoicing your customers in no time and sending professional PDF invoices with ease.

Technologies used:

Zenvoice Inc.

# Your Closet - Smart Fashion

May 2015 - Apr 2016

As a Senior Mobile Developer, I developed a new fashion-leading closet mobile app by React Native. I have strong JavaScript skills include ES6. At Closet App, I demonstrate strong client-facing qualities.

**Technologies used:** 

React Native NodeJS JavaScript

# Orlando FI

English (Fluent)

Chinese (Fluent)

# **INTERESTS**

**Table Tennis** 

Swimming

Basketball

**Badminton** 

Gitar

**SKILLS & TOOLS** 

Frontend Angular

React

JavaScript

Node.js

HTML/CSS/JQUERY

**Backend** 

Python/Django

Ruby/Rails

PHP/Laravel/Codelgniter

**JSP** 

C#

C/C++

**Others** 

DevOps Code Review Unit Testing Wireframing

Sketch Balsamiq

WordPress Shopify

**EDUCATION** 

Bachelor's Degree in **Computer Science** 

Singapore Institute of Technology 2011 - 2015

LANGUAGE